Thank you.
Crazy, nosy, please, I'll try.
Yeah, we've taken care of Angelo for good.
But it'll be a while till I'm back.
About that other photo
we've been looking into.
If you would, please send it over to me.
That's right, from Egypt.
The one the Speedwagon
Foundation found ten years ago.
I think I might have figured it out.
Later then.
And ironically, it's all thanks to him.
Josuke!
Let's be frank!
Yeah, I murdered your grandpa, but that
doesn't mean you can put me to death too!
If you kill me, you'll end up
cursed just like yours truly!
So back off if you know
what's good for you.
It's rude to point your finger at people.
Didn't your mother ever teach you that?
What the hell did you do to my hand?
You should take solace in the
fact no one's gonna execute you.
Not me, and not this guy either.
We won't be killing you.
Nor will we be turning
you into the police.
Josuke, you handle the rest.
What the hell are you psychotic
bastards planning to do?
Enjoy your eternal penance, Angelo.
Reflect on the life you stole from
my grandpa and all the others!
Damn you bastards all to hell!
I wouldn't get cocky, you little shithead!
You think you've won,
but he'll be here to butcher you
into bloody pieces soon enough!
What who is he oh you'll find out he
wears a school uniform and he's the one?
Who gave me this power
hang on you're saying
that there's someone out
there who can bestow the
power of a stand scared
yeah nice try pal but
what's so scary about
that wait he's telling the
truth about not being
born a stand user thing
is no one knew how he
obtained his powers just
think about it what if
there really is a person
who can impart stands to
others petrifying thought
isn't it do you want to
know more it happened
last year 1998 about a
month before my execution
was to be carried out i
remember that night well
it was cloudy and i
couldn't sleep with a damn
so i just sat there staring
off into the darkness
it was quiet dead quiet
then all of a sudden
it happened in that shitty
excuse for a solitary
cell there he was the guy
in the school uniform?
What the hell?
Who let you in here?
Where'd you come from?
He was holding an ancient bow and arrow.
From the looks of him, they must
have been hundreds of years old.
What are you doing?
What the hell?
I was scared shitless.
It was like my balls
crawled into my stomach.
But before I could let out a scream...
Congratulations, you survived,
and what's more, you have talent,
otherwise you'd be dead right now.
As of this moment, you've
acquired a special ability.
Or perhaps I should simply say
that I extracted it from your soul.
The more wicked the criminal,
the more talent he holds.
It's a talent that a man named
Dio once referred to as a stand.
Dio, that's what he said.
Is something the matter, Mr.
Jotaro?
What the?
You idiots.
You were so captivated by my story, you
completely forgot about my aqua necklace.
Angelo, you bastard.
Josuke, you've lost, so get
me the hell out of this rock.
I might have considered it.
If this pathetic show of yours
was actually making me mad.
What are you doing?
I told you to get me
out of this stupid rock.
Doc, if you don't get a move on,
you and your prissy-ass hair
are getting ripped apart!
Huh?
You wanna repeat that?
Take it easy, Chosuke!
What did you call my hair?
If you kill me,
the guy in the school uniform is just
gonna hunt you down to do the same to you!
I didn't say earlier, but
he lives in this town too!
Say what?
Chosuke, stand down!
I'll give him this.
He managed to piss me off.
So I thought it was only fair to repay the
dickwad by turning him
into a great work of art.
Good grief, kid.
We needed to keep him
talking a little longer. Huh?
Please don't tell me you
believed any of that crap.
You bet.
Or didn't you hear him when
he was going on about Dio?
Yeah, I heard him. Who is he?
The Joestar's greatest enemy.
Our family was fighting him
for over a hundred years.
It all came to a head ten years
ago, when we defeated him.
But there's one thing none
of us could ever figure out.
Dio didn't have a stand in the past.
So how the hell did he suddenly
gain such a powerful one in 1987?
I see.
You think he got it from the same guy?
Yeah.
I think we may have found a new
enemy in this school uniform guy.
Or it could be that the bow and
arrow is the source of this madness.
If he was right, and it's
hiding somewhere in this town,
then Angelo was just the opening act
in a horror show of epic proportions.
Good grief.
It's like Mr.
Jotaro said.
See for yourself.
There's something evil
lurking in this town.
Catastrophic dangers
closing in as we speak.
No, it's already here.
The number of missing persons reported in
Morioh has risen to 81 in this year alone.
45 of which were children,
even if some were runaways.
That's still seven to eight times
more than the national average.
It's outrageous.
Also...
Josuke's grandfather.
School's out, Koichi.
Why are you still studying there?
Let's go home.
Oh, sure.
That's a relief.
Josuke seems to be feeling better.
Yo, Angelo.
Hey, has this rock always been here?
Yeah, but it's been given a facelift.
Facelift?
Well, what do you know? Yo, Angelo.
I've been meaning to ask,
what happened to Mr. Jotaro?
Oh,
he said there was some stuff
he needed to look into,
so he went back over to the Grand Hotel.
Do you think it has to do with the town?
Sure seems like it.
I see.
We're facing a crisis.
Huh?
I think that's a... Hey, Josuke!
What?
I could be wrong, but hasn't this
house been abandoned for a few years?
Yeah, I doubt anyone
would buy this eyesore.
They'd be better off bulldozing
it and starting over.
Well, maybe they just moved in.
When I looked up at the window,
I could have sworn I saw someone.
Huh?
But that's impossible.
Did you forget where I live?
I'd have noticed if someone moved in.
And besides,
I always see real estate guys patrolling
the area looking for squatters.
Hmm.
I guess that makes sense.
How peculiar.
I hate to say it, but maybe I saw a ghost.
Freaky. Come on, dude.
Knock it off with crap like that.
Ghosts give me the willies, not
to mention I live right there.
Try keeping your nose out of other
people's business, little brat.
Nothing to say?
Koichi no! Hey!
What the hell do you think you're doing?
What?
I should be the one
asking you that question!
You and your friends are on my property!
Enough!
If it's about the newspaper,
I said we don't want any!
What's your problem?
Look, buddy, I just
lost my dad to a stroke,
and I'm still trying to figure out what
the hell my family's going to do, okay?
Come back later.
You're...
Jo...
Joseph!
You finally came back for
me after all of these years.
I've been waiting for you.
Since dad died, it's been like living
in an endless sea of depression.
You came when I needed
you most, Joseph, my love!
I'm sorry to disappoint you, but I'm
not the Joe star you're looking for.
You see, not a wrinkle on my face.
Oh, now that you mention it.
You do look younger.
Good grief.
I'm Joseph's grandson.
My name is Jotaro Kujo.
Oh, his grandson, huh?
Josuke will tell you
the rest of the story.
Tedious chit-chat drives me up the wall.
Speaking of Josuke, is he around?
Are you listening?
I asked where Josuke is.
Oh, well, the school day just
ended, so he isn't home yet. I see.
Then I'll be back tonight.
Wait you're leaving already?
Oh,
about your father—his
death was a real shame.
If Joseph Joestar were here,
he'd protect you with his life.
I'm sure he'd leap into danger
of him and keeping you safe.
But he's an old man now.
It'd be irresponsible
to let him come here.
That's why I'm here in his stead.
I've
got a bad feeling about this.
The bow and arrow,
Angelo mentioned the intel on Anyaba that
the Speed Wagon Foundation found in Egypt,
and the fact that the witch
is holding a bow and arrow.
It
really imparts the power of
the Stand to ordinary people.
people
Shit.
Another headache.
Have you completely
lost your freaking mind?
Let him go!
Let me make something real clear.
My pop bought this house.
Which means I'm not gonna
let you snoop around here.
Get what I'm saying?
I think you're the one
who's not getting it.
I'm telling you to let
go of my friend, punk.
You really don't want to tick me off.
Hey, it's not nice to call people names.
Especially when the person
you're insulting just
happens to own the property
you're trespassing on.
Jeez, don't you know how to be polite?
I know that I'm gonna smash your face
in if you don't shut your goddamn mouth.
What?
Hey, bro!
Interested as to why I
shot him with the arrow?
Because that goon is
Josuke Higashikata. Really?
So it's you.
Given that he defeated Angelo,
his stand abilities will likely
pose a nuisance to us as well.
You know about stands too?
Out with it, are you stand users?
Okuyasu, make Josuke
Higashikata disappear.
Koichi?
I had hopes he'd turn into a stand
user, and a useful one at that.
But alas, it was all for naught.
That boy's a goner.
He can't!
Hey, move it!
There's still time for me to heal his
injury using Shining Diamond's power!
Too bad.
Josuke Higashikata!
I Okuyasu Nijimura will make
you vanish, so behold the hand!
Get ready.
Out of the way, or I'll make good
on my promise to smash your face in.
Wow.
Gotta admit, you're pretty fast.
Hey, Okuyasu.
It appears manipulating a stand is a
lot like driving a car or motorcycle.
Any bumbling half-wit can get in the
driver's seat of a muscle machine,
but with only air between his ears,
he'll still be too scared to drive.
Hey bro, why the heck did you have to
go and say all of that mean stuff for?
This bastard's just a little faster
than I thought he was gonna be.
Let me remind you this
isn't a game, Okuyasu!
There was a time when the
mere thought of your stand,
the hand, sent horrific chills
streaking down my spine.
Pull yourself together!
It's time for you to kill Angelo's
murderer, Josuke Higashikata.
If you don't end him now, he'll prove
troublesome in the future. Yeah, I know.
Hey, I was talking to my bro back there.
That's not fair at all.
Oh man, you're not too
bright, are you? What?
Not bright? Why do you...
I told you to move it.
Koichi!
Oh, thank God you're still with me.
I can save you before it's two.
I have had enough!
You are not getting away!
I'm not gonna tell you again!
If you wanna piss me off, keep running!
All right, I will!
Let's see if you've got the gun!
Bastard, he's got way too much
confidence in his right hand.
Shit!
That right hand!
Something tells me... Shit!
Let go of my right hand,
you son of a bitch!
It is his right hand!
You bastard!
Stay right where you are, Josuke!
You wouldn't want to
leave your friend behind!
Something is definitely
up with your right hand.
My gut is telling me that there's
more to it than you're letting on.
You can think about my
hands once you're warm food.
This is it for you.
Koichi, hang on a little longer.
The sign.
Something's not right about it.
No passing?
If I were you, I wouldn't be so
quick to back up, you flimsy prick.
Or don't you care about
moving away from your friend?
Why don't you come a little closer?
That's it.
The sign's missing half a word.
Now I get it.
Your hand didn't make part
of that sign disappear.
It cuts out space in midair.
That's your stand's ability, isn't it?
Bingo, Josuke Higashikata!
My stand's right hand can make
whatever it grabs disappear.
But the void that's left behind?
Closes and pulls together the space.
as if it never happened.
But as for the part my hand takes away,
once my unlucky target
is sucked into the void?
I don't have a freaking
clue where it goes.
Even if you try to run, it wouldn't
matter cause I can still do this.
I just have to grab some space and then
Hey you came right to me it's
like teleporting isn't it
In case you didn't get the
memo you're up against the
Hand a Stand that even my
bro fears Try as you might,
you can't run now!
Josuke!
No matter where you try to hide,
you're always within my reach!
So go ahead, punk, make my day!
Wakeling, how is a piece of dog shit
like you able to take down Angelo?
Guess you haven't figured
out how worthless you are.
So which one of us wasn't bright again?
Now hurry up and die,
Josuke! That proves it.
You, sir, are truly an idiot. Say what?
Ah, that was a close one.
Okuyasu Nijimura.
I'd say his stand was pretty
great, but I'm not one to lie.
He's gonna be a pain in the ass when
he wakes up and tries to attack me.
I guess I better draw out his nap
with some gentle asphyxiation.
This'll definitely put the
sting of defeat in his soul.
Here we...
Koichi!
Now you've gone too far.
I'll kill you!
This arrow is irreplaceable.
There's only one, you know.
It's essential to my mission.
And losing it is not an option.
Angelo's story says it all.
There's no doubt this is the bow and
arrow that unleashed Dio's stand.
The weapon that released the world.
After Inyaba's death, someone must
have nabbed the bow and arrow.
And now they're using it
to create more stand users.
Right here in Morioh.
We've got to find and
destroy the damn thing, fast.
A villain fouler than Dio.
Or worse, a stand user who wields
even more power than the world.
We can't let either come to pass.
And if it happens again,
I'ma move so slightly?
To the arms and the lips and the face?
Of the humic and the ball
that I need to, I want to!
Come and stand a little bit closer!
Breathe in and get a bit higher!
You'll never know what
hit you when I get to you!
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you?
But ooh, I find you!
Ooh, I want you, I don't
know if I need you?
But who am I trying to find out?